sextoys.co.uk 2013-04-25

# Privacy Policy - SexToys.co.uk

We will treat all your Personal Information as confidential (although we reserve the right to disclose this information in the circumstances set out below). We will keep it on a secure server and we will fully comply with all applicable UK Data Protection and consumer legislation.

When you shop on this website, we will ask you to input and will collect personal information from you such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, delivery address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information and a password. We may also collect information about where you are on the internet (eg the URL you came from, IP address, domain types like .co.uk and .com), your browser type, the country and telephone area code where your computer is located, the pages of our website that were viewed during your visit, and any search terms that you entered on our website ("User Information"). We may collect this information even if you do not register with us.

You should be aware that this site is being monitored and may capture information about your visit that will help us improve the quality of our service.

We confirm that any personal information which you provide to us (or which is available on public registers) and any user information from which we can identify you, is held in accordance with the registration we have with the Data Commissioner's Office. We use your information only for the following purposes:  

  * Processing your orders
  * For statistical or survey purposes to improve this website and its services to you
  * To serve website content to you
  * To administer this website
  * If you consent, to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you

You agree that you do not object to us contacting you for any of the above purposes whether by telephone, e-mail or in writing and you confirm that you do not and will not consider any of the above as being a breach of any of your rights under the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003.

When you create a shopping account while ordering online you will be given the option to receive information from Net 1on1 Ltd by post or e-mail about products, promotions or special offers which we feel may be of interest to you. In the event that you do not wish to be contacted for such purposes, ensure that you tick the appropriate boxes as you go through the registration process. You may unsubscribe from our contact list at any time by following the unsubscribe link within any of our promotional emails, by contacting our Customer Service Representatives on 08000 69 69 00 between business hours.

We will not release your Personal Information to any company outside of the Net 1on1 Ltd for mailing or marketing purposes.

You should be aware that if we are requested by the police or any other regulatory or government authority investigating suspected illegal activities to provide your personal information and /or user information, we are entitled do so.

When entering any of our contests or prize draws, you provide your name, email address and mailing address. If you win, we will send the prize to the address entered and notify you by email. When you enter a contest or prize draw, you are also included in our newsletter list to receive notice of promotions, specials and new additions to the website. You may unsubscribe from this news list by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email received.

We use Cookies to keep track of your current shopping session to personalise your experience and so that you may retrieve your shopping basket at any time - if you do not accept Cookies you will be unable to use this Website.

Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy. Questions regarding this Policy should be directed to the Manager of Net 1on1 Ltd as follows:

Net 1on1 Ltd  
1 Bilton Way  
Luton  
Beds  
LU1 1UU

#### What are cookies?

Cookies are tiny text files stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages. At sextoys.co.uk we use cookies to keep track of what you have in your basket, and to remember you when you return to our site.

To order products on sextoys.co.uk, you need to have cookies enabled - see the section on Managing cookies. If you don't wish to enable cookies, you'll still be able to browse the site and use it for research purposes. Most web browsers have cookies enabled, but see Managing cookies for help to turn them on should you need to.

Please note that cookies can't harm your computer. We don't store personally identifiable information such as credit card details in cookies we create, but we do use encrypted information gathered from them to help improve your experience of the site. For example, they help us to identify and resolve errors, or to determine relevant related products to show you when you're browsing.

We're giving you this information as part of our initiative to comply with recent legislation, and to make sure we're honest and clear about your privacy when using our website. We know you'd expect nothing less from us, and please be assured that we're working on a number of other privacy and cookie-related improvements to the website.

To make full use of the online shopping and personalised features on sextoys.co.uk, your computer, tablet or mobile phone will need to accept cookies, as we can only provide you with certain personalised features of this website by using them.

Our cookies don't store sensitive information such as your name, address or payment details: they simply hold the 'key' that, once you're signed in, is associated with this information. However, if you'd prefer to restrict, block or delete cookies from sextoys.co.uk, or any other website, you can use your browser to do this. Each browser is different, so check the 'Help' menu of your particular browser (or your mobile phone's handset manual) to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

**Sextoys.co.uk 'share' tools**  
If you take the opportunity to 'share' sextoys.co.uk content with friends through social networks - such as Facebook and Twitter - you may be sent cookies from these websites. We don't control the setting of these cookies, so we suggest you check the third-party websites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.

**Further information about cookies**  
If you'd like to learn more about cookies in general and how to manage them, visit aboutcookies.org (opens in a new window - please note that we can't be responsible for the content of external websites).

When you visit sextoys.co.uk you may notice some cookies that aren't related to sextoys.co.uk. If you go on to a web page that contains embedded content, for example from YouTube, you may be sent cookies from these websites. We don't control the setting of these cookies, so we suggest you check the third-party websites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.

If cookies aren't enabled on your computer, it will mean that your shopping experience on our website will be limited to browsing and researching; you won't be able to add products to your basket and buy them.
